("Manic Monday" by The Bangles)
♪ Six o'clock already ♪
♪ I was just in the middle of a dream ♪
♪ I was kissin' Valentino ♪
♪ By a crystal-blue Italian stream ♪
♪ But I can't be late ♪
♪ 'Cause then I guess
I just won't get paid ♪
♪ These are the days ♪
♪ When you wish your
bed was already made ♪
♪ It's just another
manic Monday woah woah ♪
♪ I wish it was Sunday woah woah ♪
♪ 'Cause that's my fun
day woah woah woah woah ♪
♪ My I don't have to run day woah woah ♪
♪ It's just another manic Monday ♪
♪ Have to catch an early train ♪
♪ Got to be to work by nine ♪
♪ And if I had an aeroplane ♪
♪ I still couldn't make it on time ♪
♪ 'Cause it takes me so long ♪
♪ Just to figure out what I'm gonna wear ♪
♪ Blame it on the train ♪
♪ But the boss is already there ♪
♪ It's just another
manic Monday woah woah ♪
♪ I wish it was Sunday woah woah ♪
♪ 'Cause that's my fun
day woah woah woah woah ♪
♪ My I don't have to run day woah woah ♪
♪ It's just another manic Monday ♪
♪ Of all my nights ♪
♪ Why did my lover have
to pick last night ♪
♪ To get down ♪
♪ Last night last night ♪
♪ Doesn't it matter ♪
♪ That I have to feed the both of us ♪
♪ Employment's down ♪
♪ He tells me in his bedroom voice ♪
♪ C'mon honey let's go make some noise ♪
♪ Time it goes so fast ♪
♪ When you're having fun ♪
♪ It's just another
manic Monday woah woah ♪
♪ I wish it was Sunday woah woah ♪
♪ 'Cause that's my fun
day woah woah woah woah ♪
♪ My I don't have to run day woah woah ♪
♪ It's just another
manic Monday woah woah ♪
♪ I wish it was Sunday
woah woah woah woah ♪
♪ 'Cause that's my fun day woah woah ♪
♪ It's just another manic Monday ♪